Susan Due Pearcy collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: United Farm Workers (UFW) materials, 1970s-2014
  - Farm Worker Week, April 30-May 6, 1979, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR10; 1 color 17 1/3 x 22 1/2 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    Farm Worker Week, April 30-May 6, 1979, Children of Toil, Children of Hope, National Farm Worker Ministry ...213/386 8130, 1430 W. Olympic BI., Los Angeles, CA 90015, look for the UFW Union Label Union Label Ask for the UFW label.
  - United Farm Workers of America, AFL-CIO. Boycott Grapes & Gallo Wines, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR11; 1 color 17 3/4 x 22 3/4 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    United Farm Workers of America, AFL-CIO. Boycott Grapes & Gallo Wines.
  - Hasta La Victoria!, Lamont-Army, UFW AFL-CIO, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR12; 1 color 15 x 23 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    Hasta La Victoria!, Lamont-Army, UFW AFL-CIO.
  - Unase a La Huelga De Coachella!, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR13; 1 color 17 1/2 x 23 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    Unase a La Huelga De Coachella!
  - UFWOL, Huelga!, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR14; 1 color 18 1/2 x 24 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    UFWOL, Huelga!
  - "Across the San Joaquin Valley, across California, across the entire Southwest of the United States...," Cesar Chavez, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR15; 1 color 17 1/2 x 23 1/3 in. poster (Folder OS01)
  - Stand with us. Don't buy grapes or lettuce, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR16; 1 color 22 1/2 x 28 1/2 in. poster (Folder OS01)
- Series 3: Glen Pearcy materials, 1966-2009
  - Glen Pearcy manuscript materials, 1966-2009, manuscript materials (Box-folder 3/1)
    Glen Pearcy goes behind the iron curtain. Folder also consists of materials from the Albany Center for Children and the Southwest Georgia Project for Community Education including a child's drawing.
  - Newspapers, scrapbook, 1972-1973, manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/5)
    Story and photographs by Glen Pearcy. Newspapers are compiled from the El Malcriado newspaper, 1972.
  - Photo expenses, 1967-1968, manuscript materials (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Sermon by Glen Pearcy, undated, manuscript (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., 2016, manuscript (Box-folder 3/4)
    Log of Martin Luther King's Jr., reels along with a sermon entitled, Truth and authority, a sermon for Dr. King's Birthday.
  - Fighting For Our Lives (FFOL) Reviews, 1975-1976, manuscript materials; 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 3/5)
    UFW dinner program booklet and newspaper clippings.
  - Report on filming the Coachella strike, undated, manuscript materials (Box-folder 3/6)
    Glen Pearcy's account of the struggle of the farmers. Pearcy was asked by Chavez to document the strike.
  - In Camera summer, 1994, manuscript materials (Box-folder 3/7)
    Summer 1994 edition of the publication with an article on how Glen Pearcy's productions plays a part on the social debate.
  - The Monocle, 2006, manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/2)
    Article about Glen Pearcy and his involvement with the UFW.
- Series 4: Publications, 1972-1982
  - Prisoner, Student Interracial Ministry, undated, manuscript materials (Box-folder 3/8)
    Newsletter covering various social and civil issues.
  - United Church herald: women today, 1972, 1 newsletter (Box-folder 3/9)
  - motive, 1970-1971, 2 magazines (Box-folder 3/10)
    November 1970, April/may 1971 issue of the publication.
  - Southern Exposure, 1978, 2 magazines (Box-folder 3/11)
    Includes Generations of women in the South and South Still Life: Inside Southern Prisons
  - Southern Exposure, 1982, 2 magazines (Box-folder 3/12)
    good times and growing pains... and Who owns Appalachia?
- Series 5: Original artwork, 1967-undated
  The artwork described below are a mixture of sketches and drawings. Please note that the titles which appear in italics were supplied by the artist. All other titles were derived by the archivist.
  - Sketchbook 1 (Diary), 1967, 1 sketchbook (Box-folder 4/1)
    1 black sketchbook, diary.
  - Sketchbook 2, 1969, 1 sketchbook (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Sketchbook 3, undated, 1 sketchbook (Box-folder 4/3)
    1 spiral sketchbook. A post it on the first book says scanned, only black family scanned. Image found in other parts of the collection.
  - Sketchbook 4, May 1968, 1 sketchbook (Box-folder 4/4)
    1 spiral sketchbooks. A post it says, "scanned." The image can be found in other parts of the collection.
  - Sketchbook 5, undated, 1 9 x 12 in. spiral sketchbook (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Sketchbook 6, undated, 1 9 x 12 in. spiral sketchbook (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Sketch of a woman, undated, 1 sketch (Box-folder 4/7)
    Matted sketch of a woman.
  - Ink drawing of a man, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR101; 1 ink drawing (Box-folder 9/3)
    Ink drawing of a woman and a man.
  - Ink drawing of woman, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR102; 1 ink drawing (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Ink drawings, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR103-106; 4 matted ink drawings various sizes (Box-folder 9/5)
    Drawings by Susan Pearcy of men and women.
  - Baker Co. chicken coop, 1968, AFC 2014/028: PH02-01; 1 black-and-white 35mm slide (Box-folder 4/8)
    Etching of farmhouse by Susan Pearcy.
  - Black family, undated, AFC 2014/028: PH02-02; 1 color 35mm slide (Box-folder 4/8)
    Silkscreen print of Black Family by Susan Pearcy.
  - Beachtan House, Georgia, 1967, AFC 2014/028: PH02-03; 1 color 35mm slide (Box-folder 4/8)
    Painting by Susan Pearcy.
  - Black woman, 1967, AFC 2014/028: PH02-04; 1 color 35mm slide (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Quilt maker, 1969, AFC 2014/028: PH02-05; 1 black-and-white 35mm slide (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Barn, Halls Farm, June 1967, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR33; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS01)
  - Portrait of a man, November 1967, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR34; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS02)
  - Black Family, 1968, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR35 (Folder OS02)
  - Black-and-white template for Black Family, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR36 (Folder OS02)
  - Black-and-white template for Black Family, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR37 (Folder OS02)
  - Brown-and-white template for Black family, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR38 (Folder OS02)
  - Brown-and-black template for Black family, AFC 2014/028: OS02-GR39 (Folder OS02)
  - Watercolor of a woman sitting, July 1967, AFC 2014/028: OS03-GR40; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS03)
    1 watercolor painting
  - Watercolor of a house, July 67, AFC 2014/028: OS04-GR41; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS04)
  - Watercolor of a bedroom, AFC 2014/028: OS05-GR42; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS05)
  - Painting of a black man, 1967, AFC 2014/028: OS05-GR43; 1 drawing (Folder OS05)
  - Self portrait at Grady House, Susan Pearcy, AFC 2014/028: OS05-GR44; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS05)
  - Old cabin, out house Hall farm, June 1967, AFC 2014/028: OS05-GR45; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS05)
  - Chicken Coop-Baker Co., Georgia, 1968, AFC 2014/028: GR107; 1 black-and-white drawing (Folder OS06)
  - Man on the floor, AFC 2014/028: GR108; 1 ink sketch (Folder OS06)
    Sketch of man laying in living room floor
  - White, AFC 2014/028: GR109; 1 image (Folder OS06)
    Black-and-white image of block letters spelling out White.
  - Sketch of a woman, AFC 2014/028: GR110; 1 ink sketch (Folder OS06)
  - Wheel barrow and a shovel, AFC 2014/028: GR111; 1 ink sketch (Folder OS06)
    Ink sketch of a wheel barrow and a shovel.
  - Bicycle in the woods, AFC 2014/028: GR112; 1 ink sketch (Folder OS06)
    Ink sketch of a bicycle in the woods.
  - House in the woods, AFC 2014/028: GR113; 1 ink sketch (Folder OS06)
    Ink sketch of house in the woods.
  - Tall woman, AFC 2014/028: GR114; 1 ink sketch (Folder OS06)
    Ink sketch of tall woman, matted.
  - Two women, AFC 2014/028: GR115; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS06)
    Watercolor of two women.
  - Three women, AFC 2014/028: GR116; 1 watercolor painting (Folder OS06)
    Watercolor of three women.